<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>story on Call me Sam</title>
    <link>https://victoria.dev/hugo-theme-sam/tags/story/</link>
    <description>Recent content in story on Call me Sam</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:41:46 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://victoria.dev/hugo-theme-sam/tags/story/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>**Image** post</title>
      <link>https://victoria.dev/hugo-theme-sam/posts/image-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:41:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoria.dev/hugo-theme-sam/posts/image-post/</guid>
      <description>Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m a blog post with an image. Thanks to Open Graph and Twitter metadata, external links to this page will feature the image below.
To make this happen, set the images parameter in your post&amp;rsquo;s front-matter, like this YAML example:
images: - /posts/ideas.png </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dear Jane, regarding Mr. Bennet</title>
      <link>https://victoria.dev/hugo-theme-sam/posts/dear-jane/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Feb 2018 12:34:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoria.dev/hugo-theme-sam/posts/dear-jane/</guid>
      <description>Chapter One&amp;nbsp;¶ It is a truth universally acknowledged, that a single man in possession of a good fortune, must be in want of a wife.
However little known the feelings or views of such a man may be on his first entering a neighbourhood, this truth is so well fixed in the minds of the surrounding families, that he is considered the rightful property of some one or other of their daughters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oh, Alice</title>
      <link>https://victoria.dev/hugo-theme-sam/posts/oh-alice/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Feb 2018 12:32:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://victoria.dev/hugo-theme-sam/posts/oh-alice/</guid>
      <description>Nor did such soothing scenes, however temporary, fail of at least as temporary an effect on Ahab. But if these secret golden keys did seem to open in him his own secret golden treasuries, yet did his breath upon them prove but tarnishing. Alice opened the door and found that it led into a small passage, not much larger than a rat-hole: she knelt down and looked along the passage into the loveliest garden you ever saw.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
